Guide to the Frank L. Benepe Records 1880-1893
Montana State University-Bozeman Library
Frank L. Benepe Records
1880-1893
Montana State University Library, Merrill G. Burlingame Special Collections P.O. Box 173320 Bozeman, MT 59717-3320 United States Phone (406) 994-4242 Fax (406) 994-2851 http://www.lib.montana.edu/archives/ University Archivist spcoll@www.lib.montana.edu
Collection 630, MtBC, us
Benepe, Frank L., b. 1851
14.8 linear feet
The Frank L. Benepe Records include business related documents and correspondence. Of particular interest are the papers regarding Benepe's business with the United States Geological Survey, the Bureau of Indian Affairs and the United States army, including transactions with the post at Yellowstone National Park, Camp Sheridan.
Historical Note
Frank L. Benepe came to Bozeman, Montana in 1877. After teaching for two years, he established the Benepe and Davidson Company in 1879. His first business venture, Benepe quickly became a primary supplier of agricultural implements and farm machinery for the entire region. By 1883, Benepe purchased John B. Davidson's interest in the business. The Bozeman Implement, Harness and Carriage Company was organized by Benepe in 1890. Two years later, the name was changed to Benepe-Owenhouse Company to reflect a partnership with E. J. Owenhouse. Other business interests included extensive grain operations throughout the Gallatin valley. By the end of the nineteenth century it is reported that Benepe bought and sold more grain than any other person in the county. His vast grain operations briefly included a controlling interest in the Belgrade Grain and Produce Company. Outside of his public business ventures, Benepe owned a large grain and stock ranch in Gallatin Valley and a stock farm in Bozeman where he raised Hereford cattle. Benepe served as mayor of Bozeman for two terms, served as a member of the Free and Accepted Masons, and was the director of the Bozeman Silver Cornet Band throughout the late 1880s. In 1882 Benepe married Nettie Trent of Kansas. Together the couple had five children; Byron who died at 18 months, Frank L. Jr., Ellen E., Genevieve A., and Lucien.
This collection primarily includes business related documents and correspondence. Of particular interest are the papers regarding Benepe's business with the United States Geological Survey, the Bureau of Indian Affairs and the United States army, including transactions with the post at Yellowstone National Park, Camp Sheridan. Throughout the years Benepe held various grain contracts and provided supplies to the before mentioned agencies.
Series 1 Correspondence, 1884-1891
Series 2 Legal Documents, 1885-1891
Series 3 Promotional Material, 1885-1890
Series 4 Government Documents, 1886-1891
Series 5 Financial Documents, 1880-1893
This collection is open for research.
Business papers collected by Frank Benepe and other business associates were donated to Special Collections by Lucien Benepe in 1968.
Geological Survey (U.S.); United States-Army-Supplies and stores; United States-Bureau of Indian Affairs
Camp Sheridan (Wyo.); Yellowstone National Park
Agricultural implement industry-Montana-Bozeman; Grain trade-Montana-Bozeman
Business records-Montana-Bozeman
Businessmen-Montana-Bozeman; Government contractors-Montana-Bozeman
Native Americans; Retail Trade; Montana
- Correspondence, 1884-1891; Series 1
  This series is arranged in chronological order and primarily contains business correspondence. In this case, business correspondence denotes written orders for merchandise from any of the related Benepe businesses. Throughout the series invoices and receipts are occasionally found. These items are included in the series only when they pertain to a specific letter or order. Correspondence between Benepe and the government agencies can be found in Series 4.
  - 1884 (Box-folder 1/1)
  - January-May 1885 (Box-folder 1/2)
  - June-July 1885 (Box-folder 1/3)
  - August-September 1885 (Box-folder 1/4)
  - October 1885 (Box-folder 1/5)
  - November 1885 (Box-folder 1/6)
  - December 1885 (Box-folder 1/7)
  - January-February 1886 (Box-folder 2/1)
  - March 1886 (Box-folder 2/2)
  - April-May 1886 (Box-folder 2/3)
  - June 1886 (Box-folder 2/4)
  - July 1886 (Box-folder 2/5)
  - August 1886 (Box-folder 2/6)
  - September 1886 (Box-folder 2/7)
  - October 1886 (Box-folder 2/8)
  - November 1886 (Box-folder 2/9)
  - December 1886 (Box-folder 2/10)
  - January 1887 (Box-folder 3/1)
  - February 1887 (Box-folder 3/2)
  - March 1887 (Box-folder 3/3)
  - April 1887 (Box-folder 3/4)
  - May 1887 (Box-folder 3/5)
  - June 1887 (Box-folder 3/6)
  - July 1887 (Box-folder 3/7)
  - August 1887 (Box-folder 4/1)
  - September 1887 (Box-folder 4/2)
  - October 1887 (Box-folder 4/3)
  - November 1887 (Box-folder 4/4)
  - December 1887 (Box-folder 4/5)
  - January 1888 (Box-folder 5/1)
  - February 1888 (Box-folder 5/2)
  - March 1888 (Box-folder 5/3)
  - April 1888 (Box-folder 5/4)
  - May 1888 (Box-folder 5/5)
  - June 1888 (Box-folder 5/6)
  - July 1888 (Box-folder 6/1)
  - August 1888 (Box-folder 6/2)
  - September 1888 (Box-folder 6/3)
  - October 1888 (Box-folder 6/4)
  - November 1888 (Box-folder 7/1)
  - December 1888 (Box-folder 7/2)
  - January 1889 (Box-folder 7/3)
  - February 1889 (Box-folder 7/4)
  - March 1889 (Box-folder 8/1)
  - April 1889 (Box-folder 8/2)
  - May 1889 (Box-folder 8/3)
  - June 1889 (Box-folder 8/4)
  - July 1889 (Box-folder 9/1)
  - August 1889 (Box-folder 9/2)
  - September 1889 (Box-folder 9/3)
  - October 1889 (Box-folder 9/4)
  - November 1889 (Box-folder 9/5)
  - December 1889 (Box-folder 10/1)
  - 1889 (Box-folder 10/2)
  - January 1890 (Box-folder 10/3)
  - February 1890 (Box-folder 10/4)
  - March 1890 (Box-folder 10/5)
  - April 1890 (Box-folder 10/6)
  - May 1890 (Box-folder 10/7)
  - June 1890 (Box-folder 10/8)
  - July-August 1890 (Box-folder 10/9)
  - September-October 1890 (Box-folder 10/10)
  - November-December 1890 (Box-folder 10/11)
  - 1891 (Box-folder 11/1)
  - January 1891 (Box-folder 11/2)
  - February 1891 (Box-folder 11/3)
  - March 1891 (Box-folder 11/4)
  - April 1891 (Box-folder 11/5)
  - May 1891 (Box-folder 11/6)
  - June 1891 (Box-folder 11/7)
  - July 1891 (Box-folder 11/8)
  - August 1891 (Box-folder 11/9)
  - September 1891 (Box-folder 11/10)
  - October 1891 (Box-folder 11/11)
  - November 1891 (Box-folder 11/12)
  - December 1891 (Box-folder 11/13)
  - Letter Press Book, 1887 (Box-folder 12/1)
  - Letter Press Book, E. J. Owenhouse, 1888-1889 (Box-folder 12/2)
  - Letter Press Book, Frank Benepe, 1888-1889 (Box-folder 12/3)
  - Letter Press Book, Frank Benepe, 1887 (Box-folder 12/4)
- Legal Documents, 1885-1891; Series 2
  This series contains insurance policies, city licenses, and other miscellaneous legal documents that include, but is not limited to, court papers and property deeds.
  - Legal Documents, 1885-1890 (Box-folder 13/1)
  - Insurance Policies, 1889 (Box-folder 13/2)
  - E. J. Owenhouse City Licenses, 1885-1891 (Box-folder 13/3)
- Promotional Material, 1885-1890; Series 3
  Included are various advertisements and partial sale catalogs pertaining to merchandise sold through the various Benepe businesses. Also included in this series is a partial E. J. Owenhouse catalog of an unknown date. A complete version of this catalog is located in Special Collections at SF309.9.085.
  - Partial E. J. Owenhouse Catalog (Box-folder 13/4)
  - Advertisements (Box-folder 13/5)
- Government Contracts, 1886-1891; Series 4
  This series contains contracts, order requests and communications between the Benepe businesses and various government agencies. Included are the flour contract for the Blackfeet and Crow reservations (1886-1887), U.S. Geological Survey correspondence and merchandise requests, the Camp Sheridan (Yellowstone National Park) hay contract (1887-1888) and the 1886 Fort Ellis hay contract. The material of this series is arranged according to the specific agency or contract. For example, a folder may include the contract and all communications between Benepe and the government agents.
  - U.S. Geological Survey Correspondence, 1888-1891 (Box-folder 14/1)
  - U.S. Bureau of Indian Affairs, Flour Contract: Blackfeet/Crow, 1886-1887 (Box-folder 14/2)
  - Camp Sheridan (Wyoming) Hay Contract, 1887-1888 (Box-folder 14/3)
  - Fort Ellis Hay Contract, 1886 (Box-folder 14/4)
- Financial Documents, 1880-1893; Series 5
  Series 5 contains financial and business related documents. Included are invoices, receipts, day books, ledgers, scale record books, bank deposit books, store credit slips, and more. The boxes containing the title "Invoices/Receipts" reflect the original arrangement by Frank Benepe and all efforts were made to maintain his original order. Store charge slips do not have years attached to the dates and are filed accordingly. The series is arranged by document type.
  - Invoices/Receipts, 1880-1881 (Box-folder 15/1)
  - Invoices/Receipts, January-June 1882 (Box-folder 15/2)
  - Invoices/Receipts, July-December 1882 (Box-folder 15/3)
  - Invoices/Receipts, January-June 1883 (Box-folder 15/4)
  - Invoices/Receipts, July-December 1883 (Box-folder 15/5)
  - Invoices/Receipts, January-June 1884 (Box-folder 15/6)
  - Invoices/Receipts, July-December 1884 (Box-folder 15/7)
  - Invoices/Receipts, January-June 1885 (Box-folder 15/8)
  - Invoices/Receipts, July-December 1885 (Box-folder 15/9)
  - Invoices/Receipts, January 1886 (Box-folder 16/1)
  - Invoices/Receipts, February 1886 (Box-folder 16/2)
  - Invoices/Receipts, March 1886 (Box-folder 16/3)
  - Invoices/Receipts, April 1886 (Box-folder 16/4)
  - Invoices/Receipts, May 1886 (Box-folder 16/5)
  - Invoices/Receipts, June 1886 (Box-folder 16/6)
  - Invoices/Receipts, July 1886 (Box-folder 16/7)
  - Invoices/Receipts, August 1886 (Box-folder 16/8)
  - Invoices/Receipts, September 1886 (Box-folder 16/9)
  - Invoices/Receipts, October 1886 (Box-folder 16/10)
  - Invoices/Receipts, November 1886 (Box-folder 16/11)
  - Invoices/Receipts, December 1886 (Box-folder 16/12)
  - Invoices/Receipts, February 1887 (Box-folder 17/2)
  - Invoices/Receipts, March 1887 (Box-folder 17/3)
  - Invoices/Receipts, April 1887 (Box-folder 17/4)
  - Invoices/Receipts, May 1887 (Box-folder 17/5)
  - Invoices/Receipts, June 1887 (Box-folder 17/6)
  - Invoices/Receipts, July 1887 (Box-folder 17/7)
  - Invoices/Receipts, August 1887 (Box-folder 17/8)
  - Invoices/Receipts, September 1887 (Box-folder 17/9)
  - Invoices/Receipts, October 1887 (Box-folder 17/10)
  - Invoices/Receipts, November 1887 (Box-folder 17/11)
  - Invoices/Receipts, December 1887 (Box-folder 17/12)
  - Invoices/Receipts, January 1888 (Box-folder 18/1)
  - Invoices/Receipts, February 1888 (Box-folder 18/2)
  - Invoices/Receipts, March 1888 (Box-folder 18/3)
  - Invoices/Receipts, April 1888 (Box-folder 18/4)
  - Invoices/Receipts, May 1888 (Box-folder 18/5)
  - Invoices/Receipts, June 1888 (Box-folder 18/6)
  - Invoices/Receipts, July 1888 (Box-folder 18/7)
  - Invoices/Receipts, August 1888 (Box-folder 18/8)
  - Invoices/Receipts, September 1888 (Box-folder 18/9)
  - Invoices/Receipts, October 1888 (Box-folder 18/10)
  - Invoices/Receipts, November 1888 (Box-folder 18/11)
  - Invoices/Receipts, December 1888 (Box-folder 18/12)
  - Invoices/Receipts, January 1889 (Box-folder 19/1)
  - Invoices/Receipts, February 1889 (Box-folder 19/2)
  - Invoices/Receipts, March 1889 (Box-folder 19/3)
  - Invoices/Receipts, April 1889 (Box-folder 19/4)
  - Invoices/Receipts, May 1889 (Box-folder 19/5)
  - Invoices/Receipts, June 1889 (Box-folder 19/6)
  - Invoices/Receipts, July 1889 (Box-folder 19/7)
  - Invoices/Receipts, August 1889 (Box-folder 20/1)
  - Invoices/Receipts, September 1889 (Box-folder 20/2)
  - Invoices/Receipts, October 1889 (Box-folder 20/3)
  - Invoices/Receipts, November 1889 (Box-folder 20/4)
  - Invoices/Receipts, December 1889 (Box-folder 20/5)
  - Invoices/Receipts, January 1890 (Box-folder 20/6)
  - Invoices/Receipts, February 1890 (Box-folder 20/7)
  - Invoices/Receipts, March 1890 (Box-folder 20/8)
  - Invoices/Receipts, April 1890 (Box-folder 20/9)
  - Invoices/Receipts, May 1890 (Box-folder 20/10)
  - Invoices/Receipts, June 1890 (Box-folder 20/11)
  - Invoices/Receipts, July 1890 (Box-folder 20/12)
  - Invoices/Receipts, August-December 1890 (Box-folder 20/13)
  - Invoices/Receipts, January 1891 (Box-folder 21/1)
  - Invoices/Receipts, February 1891 (Box-folder 21/2)
  - Invoices/Receipts, March 1891 (Box-folder 21/3)
  - Invoices/Receipts, April 1891 (Box-folder 21/4)
  - Invoices/Receipts, May 1891 (Box-folder 21/5)
  - Invoices/Receipts, June 1891 (Box-folder 21/6)
  - Invoices/Receipts, July 1891 (Box-folder 21/7)
  - Invoices/Receipts, August 1891 (Box-folder 21/8)
  - Invoices/Receipts, September 1891 (Box-folder 21/9)
  - Invoices/Receipts, October 1891 (Box-folder 21/10)
  - Invoices/Receipts, November 1891 (Box-folder 21/11)
  - Invoices/Receipts, December 1891 (Box-folder 21/12)
  - Invoices/Receipts, 1892-1893 (Box-folder 21/13)
  - Invoices/Receipts, undated (Box-folder 21/14)
  - Store Charge Slips, January (Box-folder 22/1)
  - Store Charge Slips, February (Box-folder 22/2)
  - Store Charge Slips, March (Box-folder 22/3)
  - Store Charge Slips, April (Box-folder 22/4)
  - Store Charge Slips, May (Box-folder 22/5)
  - Store Charge Slips, June (Box-folder 22/6)
  - Store Charge Slips, July (Box-folder 22/7)
  - Store Charge Slips, August (Box-folder 22/8)
  - Store Charge Slips, September-December (Box-folder 22/9)
  - Northern Pacific Shipping Receipts, March 7, 1887-November 1, 1889 (Box-folder 23/1)
  - Northern Pacific Shipping Receipts, January-June 1886 (Box-folder 23/2)
  - Northern Pacific Shipping Receipts, July-December 1886 (Box-folder 23/3)
  - Northern Pacific Shipping Receipts, January-June 1887 (Box-folder 23/4)
  - Northern Pacific Shipping Receipts, July-August 1887 (Box-folder 23/5)
  - Northern Pacific Shipping Receipts, September-October 1887 (Box-folder 23/6)
  - Northern Pacific Shipping Receipts, November-December 1887 (Box-folder 23/7)
  - Northern Pacific Shipping Receipts, January-June 1888 (Box-folder 23/8)
  - Northern Pacific Shipping Receipts, July-December 1888 (Box-folder 24/1)
  - Northern Pacific Shipping Receipts, January-July 1889 (Box-folder 24/2)
  - Northern Pacific Shipping Receipts, July-December 1889 (Box-folder 24/3)
  - Northern Pacific Shipping Receipts, 1890 (Box-folder 24/4)
  - Northern Pacific Shipping Receipts, April-June 1891 (Box-folder 24/5)
  - Northern Pacific Shipping Receipts, July-December 1891 (Box-folder 24/6)
  - Northern Pacific Shipping Receipts, 1892 (Box-folder 24/7)
  - Bills of Lading, 1887 (Box-folder 25/1)
  - Bills of Lading, 1888 (Box-folder 25/2)
  - Bills of Lading, 1889 (Box-folder 25/3)
  - Bills of Lading, April 1892 (Box-folder 25/4)
  - Bills of Lading, May 1892 (Box-folder 25/5)
  - Bills of Lading, June 1892 (Box-folder 25/6)
  - Bills of Lading, July 1892 (Box-folder 25/7)
  - Bills of Lading, August 1892 (Box-folder 25/8)
  - Bills of Lading, September 1892 (Box-folder 25/9)
  - Bills of Lading, October 1892 (Box-folder 25/10)
  - Bills of Lading, November 1892 (Box-folder 25/11)
  - Bills of Lading, December 1892 (Box-folder 25/12)
  - Bills of Lading, January 1893 (Box-folder 25/13)
  - Bills of Lading, February 1893 (Box-folder 25/14)
  - Bills of Lading, March 1893 (Box-folder 25/15)
  - Bills of Lading, April 1893 (Box-folder 25/16)
  - Canceled Checks, 1881 (Box-folder 26/1)
  - Canceled Checks, 1882 (Box-folder 26/2)
  - Canceled Checks, 1883 (Box-folder 26/3)
  - Canceled Checks, 1884 (Box-folder 26/4)
  - Canceled Checks, February 1885 (Box-folder 26/5)
  - Canceled Checks, March 1885 (Box-folder 26/6)
  - Canceled Checks, May 1885 (Box-folder 26/7)
  - Canceled Checks, June 1885 (Box-folder 26/8)
  - Canceled Checks, July 1885 (Box-folder 26/9)
  - Canceled Checks, August 1885 (Box-folder 26/10)
  - Canceled Checks, September 1885 (Box-folder 26/11)
  - Canceled Checks, October 1885 (Box-folder 26/12)
  - Canceled Checks, November 1885 (Box-folder 26/13)
  - Canceled Checks, December 1885 (Box-folder 26/14)
  - Canceled Checks, January 1886 (Box-folder 27/1)
  - Canceled Checks, February 1886 (Box-folder 27/2)
  - Canceled Checks, March 1886 (Box-folder 27/3)
  - Canceled Checks, April 1886 (Box-folder 27/4)
  - Canceled Checks, May 1886 (Box-folder 27/5)
  - Canceled Checks, June 1886 (Box-folder 27/6)
  - Canceled Checks, July 1886 (Box-folder 27/7)
  - Canceled Checks, August 1886 (Box-folder 27/8)
  - Canceled Checks, September 1886 (Box-folder 27/9)
  - Canceled Checks, October 1886 (Box-folder 27/10)
  - Canceled Checks, November 1886 (Box-folder 27/11)
  - Canceled Checks, December 1886 (Box-folder 27/12)
  - Canceled Checks, January 1887 (Box-folder 27/13)
  - Canceled Checks, February 1887 (Box-folder 27/14)
  - Canceled Checks, March 1887 (Box-folder 27/15)
  - Canceled Checks, April 1887 (Box-folder 27/16)
  - Canceled Checks, June 1887 (Box-folder 27/17)
  - Canceled Checks, July 1887 (Box-folder 27/18)
  - Canceled Checks, August 1887 (Box-folder 28/1)
  - Canceled Checks, September 1887 (Box-folder 28/2)
  - Canceled Checks, October 1887 (Box-folder 28/3)
  - Canceled Checks, November 1887 (Box-folder 28/4)
  - Canceled Checks, December 1887 (Box-folder 28/5)
  - Canceled Checks, January 1888 (Box-folder 28/6)
  - Canceled Checks, February 1888 (Box-folder 28/7)
  - Canceled Checks, March 1888 (Box-folder 28/8)
  - Canceled Checks, April 1888 (Box-folder 28/9)
  - Canceled Checks, May 1888 (Box-folder 28/10)
  - Canceled Checks, June 1888 (Box-folder 28/11)
  - Canceled Checks, July 1888 (Box-folder 28/12)
  - Canceled Checks, August 1888 (Box-folder 28/13)
  - Canceled Checks, September 1888 (Box-folder 28/14)
  - Canceled Checks, October 1888 (Box-folder 28/15)
  - Canceled Checks, November 1888 (Box-folder 28/16)
  - Check Stubs (Bound), March 1, 1884-March 18, 1885 (Box-folder 29/1)
  - Check Stubs (Bound), March 30-November 11, 1885 (Box-folder 29/2)
  - Check Stubs (Bound), May 6-June 19, 1886 (Box-folder 29/3)
  - Check Stubs (Bound), December 22, 1886-March 14, 1887 (Box-folder 29/4)
  - Check Stubs (Bound), May 5-September 17, 1887 (Box-folder 29/5)
  - Check Stubs (Bound), September 19-November 26, 1887 (Box-folder 29/6)
  - Check Stubs (Bound), November 26, 1887-January 26, 1888 (Box-folder 29/7)
  - Check Stubs (Bound), January 27-May 11, 1888 (Box-folder 29/8)
  - Check Stubs (Bound), May 11-August 10, 1888 (Box-folder 30/1)
  - Check Stubs (Bound), August 11-November 14, 1888 (Box-folder 30/2)
  - Check Stubs (Bound), September 3-December 30, 1890 (Box-folder 30/3)
  - Bank Account Statement Books, January 15, 1881-April 17, 1882 (Box-folder 30/4)
  - Bank Account Statement Books, April 27-December 1, 1883 (Box-folder 30/5)
  - Bank Account Statement Books, December 3, 1883-September 29, 1884 (Box-folder 30/6)
  - Bank Account Statement Books, October 1, 1885-September 1, 1886 (Box-folder 30/7)
  - Bank Account Statement Books, October 2, 1886-October 28, 1887 (Box-folder 30/8)
  - Bank Account Statement Books, November 1, 1887-August 30, 1888 (Box-folder 30/9)
  - Scale Record Books, July 5, 1882-November 20, 1882 (Box-folder 31/1)
  - Scale Record Books, November 22, 1882-January 30, 1883 (Box-folder 31/2)
  - Scale Record Books, January 30-May 17, 1883 (Box-folder 31/3)
  - Scale Record Books, September 21-November 22, 1883 (Box-folder 31/4)
  - Scale Record Books, November 23, 1883-March 6, 1884 (Box-folder 31/5)
  - Scale Record Books, March 10-August 2, 1884 (Box-folder 31/6)
  - Scale Record Books, August 4-December 13, 1884 (Box-folder 31/7)
  - Scale Record Books, December 15, 1884-June 9, 1885 (Box-folder 31/8)
  - Scale Record Books, June 12-September 30, 1885 (Box-folder 31/9)
  - Scale Record Books, October 1-December 31, 1885 (Box-folder 31/10)
  - Scale Record Books, January 1-March 3, 1886 (Box-folder 32/1)
  - Scale Record Books, November 11, 1885-January 27, 1886 (Box-folder 32/2)
  - Scale Record Books, January 27-May 6, 1886 (Box-folder 32/3)
  - Scale Record Books, May 6-August 7, 1886 (Box-folder 32/4)
  - Scale Record Books, August 9-October 1, 1886 (Box-folder 32/5)
  - Scale Record Books, October 1-November 23, 1886 (Box-folder 32/6)
  - Scale Record Books, January 10-September 22, 1887 (Box-folder 32/7)
  - Scale Record Books, November 23, 1886-March 3, 1887 (Box-folder 32/8)
  - Scale Record Books, March 4-September 1, 1887 (Box-folder 32/9)
  - Scale Record Books, September 2-October 7, 1887 (Box-folder 32/10)
  - Scale Record Books, October 27-November 8, 1887 (Box-folder 32/11)
  - Scale Record Books, November 8-November 23, 1887 (Box-folder 33/1)
  - Scale Record Books, November 23-December 17, 1987 (Box-folder 33/2)
  - Scale Record Books, September 22-December 15, 1887 (Box-folder 33/3)
  - Scale Record Books, December 17, 1887-January 18, 1888 (Box-folder 33/4)
  - Scale Record Books, December 15, 1887-May 21, 1888 (Box-folder 33/5)
  - Scale Record Books, January 19-May 23, 1888 (Box-folder 33/6)
  - Scale Record Books, May 22-September 22, 1888 (Box-folder 33/7)
  - Scale Record Books, May 23-October 9, 1888 (Box-folder 33/8)
  - Scale Record Books, September 22-November 8, 1888 (Box-folder 33/9)
  - Scale Record Books, October 9-November 8, 1888 (Box-folder 33/10)
  - Scale Record Books, November 7-December 31, 1888 (Box-folder 34/1)
  - Scale Record Books, November 8-December 12, 1888 (Box-folder 34/2)
  - Scale Record Books, December 31, 1888-February 23, 1889 (Box-folder 34/3)
  - Scale Record Books, December 12, 1888-March 3, 1889 (Box-folder 34/4)
  - Scale Record Books, February 23-May 13, 1889 (Box-folder 34/5)
  - Scale Record Books, March 4-August 5, 1889 (Box-folder 34/6)
  - Scale Record Books, May 13-August 15, 1889 (Box-folder 34/7)
  - Scale Record Books, August 6-October 10, 1889 (Box-folder 34/8)
  - Scale Record Books, August 5-October 10, 1889 (Box-folder 34/9)
  - Scale Record Books, October 10-November 25, 1889 (Box-folder 35/1)
  - Scale Record Books, November 25, 1889-January 25, 1890 (Box-folder 35/2)
  - Scale Record Books, January 25-May 12, 1890 (Box-folder 35/3)
  - Scale Record Books, May 12-August 1, 1890 (Box-folder 35/4)
  - Scale Record Books, August 1-October 17, 1890 (Box-folder 35/5)
  - Scale Record Books, October 17-November 15, 1890 (Box-folder 35/6)
  - Scale Record Books, November 15, 1890-February 6, 1891 (Box-folder 35/7)
  - Deering and Company Papers/Contracts, 1884-1887 (Box-folder 36/1)
  - Benepe Inventory/Trial Balance, undated (Box-folder 36/2)
  - Benepe Inventory/Trial Balance, February 1887 (Box-folder 36/3)
  - Benepe Inventory/Trial Balance, March 1887 (Box-folder 36/4)
  - Benepe Inventory/Trial Balance, April 1887 (Box-folder 36/5)
  - Benepe Balance Sheet, January 1889 (Box-folder 36/6)
  - Frost and Manderville Day Book, and Frank Benepe Day Book, 1882-1883; 1887 (Box-folder 36/7)
  - Day Book, May-September 1886 (Box-folder 37/1)
  - Day Book, September 1887-January 1888 (Box-folder 37/2)
  - Ledger, 1885-1887 (Box-folder 37/3)
  - Benepe and Davidson Ledger, 1882-1883 (Box-folder 37/4)
  - Cash Ledger, October 1884-May 1885 (Box-folder 38/1)
  - Cash Book, 1884-1886 (Box-folder 38/2)
  - Elevator Ledger, 1891-1892 (Box-folder 38/3)
  - Day Book, October 1886-January 1887 (Box-folder 38/4)
  - Day Book, April 1885-October 1885 (Box-folder 38/5)
  - Invoice/Receipt Book, 1883-1887 (Box-folder 39/1)